http://www.coastalpoodlerescue.org/about-us/privacy-policy.html

Coastal Poodle Rescue rehabilitates unwanted, abused and abandoned poodles and then places them in loving and responsible homes to live out their lives as cherished family members.
(321) 459-2652
About UsOur HistoryPrivacy PolicyCurrent StatsContact UsAdoptable DogsSpecial NeedsSeniors For SeniorsTake Me HomeHow You Can HelpSponsor A PoodleFosterAdoptDonateVolunteerHappy TailsHappy EndingsBefore & AfterMore InfoAbout RescueIs A Poodle For MeOther RescuesUseful LinksPoodle FactsNews & EventsNews & AnnouncementsUpcoming EventsVideo, Newsletters & Sponsor History
Coastal Poodle Rescue Privacy Policy
Personal Information We Collect
Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with Coastal Poodle Rescue. We take seriously the trust you place in us. Coastal Poodle Rescue will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.
On the Coastal Poodle Rescue web site, you can make donations, request an adoption, participate as a volunteer, make information requests, or sign up to receive news and information from us. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone, email address, user IDs and passwords, household information and contact preferences.
How We Use Your Information
Coastal Poodle Rescue uses your information to help us understand your needs and interests and to process your application correctly. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete an adoption or perform a volunteer service, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits, and to personalize notices of upcoming events.
Coastal Poodle Rescue will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Coastal Poodle Rescue will not share your personal information with third parties except in responding to your requests for information or services.
Suppliers and service providers, such as veterinarians, are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Coastal Poodle Rescue and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Coastal Poodle Rescue. These service providers may change or we may contract with additional service providers to expand or improve our services. Coastal Poodle Rescue will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action, subpoena, or local law.
Coastal Poodle Rescue or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or some or all of their respective assets could be acquired. If such a combination or acquisition occurs, Coastal Poodle Rescue will make every reasonable effort to notify you in the event we share with the merging or acquiring entity some or all of your personal information to continue serving you.
Access and Accuracy
Coastal Poodle Rescue strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. We have put in place managerial data standards review processes and technological tools to maintain customer data accuracy. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your data. Certain areas of Coastal Poodle Rescue's web site may limit access to specific individuals through the use of passwords and other personal identifiers. The most effective way to view and change your personal information is to update your profile online.
Security
Coastal Poodle Rescue is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Coastal Poodle Rescue has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window.
This document was last updated April, 2006
Sponsor A PoodleFosterAdoptDonateVolunteerMember Login
Copyright © 2012Coastal Poodle Rescue, Inc.P.O. Box 121142Melbourne, FL 32912
editor login
Designed by Sites By Sequoia.
